Joseph Oluwadara

SMART CONTRACT ENGINEER & RESEARCHER

<u>jsatimehin@gmail.com</u>

<u>Github</u> <u>Twitter</u>

Telegram: Josephdara

PROFILE

I am a Smart Contract Engineer and Security Researcher, experienced in writing and auditing complex solidity smart contracts. With a deep level understanding of the EVM, I have audited both simple and complex codebases totalling over 200,000 SLOC in public audit contests, uncovering 50+ Critical, High and Medium severity bugs.

With multiple years of smart development & auditing experience, I have worked on multiple protocols integrating different contract types such as: AMMs, Fungible and Non Fungible tokens, Sales contracts, Auction contracts, Liquidity staking contracts, Account Abstraction Wallets, Vaults, Factories, Proxies and Upgradeable contracts.

I currently do smart contract audits at Code4rena and Cantina. I also participate in different CTFs and I have completed a few such as Ethernaut from Openzeppelin, Damn Vulnerable Defi, Secureum Bootcamp and more.

Some of my regular development tools and languages include:

- Solidity & Assembly: YUL
- Foundry
- Hardhat & Web3.js
- JavaScript
- Typescript
- Rust

EXPERIENCE

Smart Contract Security Researcher

April 2023 - Present

- Participated in 20+ Audits Contests in Code4rena finding 40 High and medium severity issues, vetted by judges and accepted by protocols.
- Some prominent wins includes :
 - **Y**Top 9 in the Good Entry Contest
 - YTop 9 in the WildCat Contest
 - YTop 5 in the Ethena Contest
 - YSolo finding in the Zetachain Contest

Here is my Code4rena Profile for review: josephdara on Code4rena

• Other bugs were found on Sherlock and ImmuneFi

Developer Advocate (Contract)

TNTMAX

October 2023 - March 2024

- Represented INTMAX as a speaker at the Google DevFest Lagos stage, the largest tech event in West Africa.
- Represented INTMAX in the Africa Tech Summit, Nairobi.
- Represented INTMAX as a Mentor for the Web3Bridge ZK Cohort.
- Created educational content and articles, explaining different parts of the protocol.

Blockchain Developer (Contract)

Astra Metaverse

September 2022 - January 2023

- Created an ERC 1155 token smart contract and minter
- Created a Metaverse Marketplace smart contract
- Writing APIs to connect with the smart contracts on the blockchain

Blockchain Developer

COLLECT WAVES

May 2022 - December 2022

- Created & Tested an Music NFT smart Contract
- Designed an NFT market place smart contract and NFT minter
- Writing APIs to connect with the smart contracts on the blockchain
- Creation of Tokens.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, MATHEMATICS

Federal University of Abeokuta, Ogun, Nigeria. 2018 - 2022